《越狱》前情回顾
Previously onPrison Break
关于那个人
There's something about this guy.
他似乎知道
It's like he knows where
我们要去哪里和我们在想什么 如果是真的话
we're going and what we're thinking. If that's true,
不久他就能发现在犹他的钱...
it's just a matter of time before he finds out about the money in Utah
我们怎么去墨西哥...
our way into Mexico...
所有事
Everything.
...会有律师
...have an attorney present
出现在现在或者将来质询过程中
during questioning now or in the future...
凯若琳 他们正带她进去
Caroline,they're taking her in.
当然  我会看着她
Of course. I'll keep an eye on her.
你确实做了 爸爸
You did it,Dad.
像我说的那样做
Just do as you're told.
不然结果会
Otherwise there will be consequences
牵涉到我们两个人
that will affect us all.
我爸是空军上校
My dad's an Air Force colonel.
当我告诉他我和一个男孩子在一个旅馆里
When I told him I was staying in a hotel with a guy that I
而且是一个我有点喜欢的男孩子
maybe sorta liked,
他勃然大怒了
he lost it.
你在这里干什么? 玛丽克鲁兹在哪儿?
What are you doing here? Where's Maricruz?
她现在和我在一起了
She's with me now.
告诉我她在哪儿
Don't push it.
嘿  费尔南多  慢点
Hey,Fernando,slow down,man.
我刚才正想告诉你  婚礼在拉斯维加斯举行
I was trying to tell you,the wedding is in Vegas.
这会是谁?
Which one of them was it?
可能是斯科菲尔德
Might be Scofield.
我们还可能
Probably gonna find
在这里找到他哥哥的尸体
his brother in there,too.
去哪儿 先生?
Where to,sir?
犹他
Utah.
今天早上伊利诺斯州有关部门
This morning,authorities in Illinois
发布了关于越狱最新情况
issued an update on the escaped convicts
到现在为止  从福克斯河越狱的八个人中
known until now as the Fox River Eight
芝加哥黑帮老大约翰 阿布鲁奇
Chicago mob boss John Abruzzi
昨晚在华盛顿一家汽车旅馆外被击毙
was gunned down outside a Washington D.C. motel last night
是由于调查人员获得了线人的消息
after investigators received a tip from an informant.
其余七人仍旧在逃
The other seven escapees
依然极度危险
are still at large and considered dangerous.
我没想到阿布鲁奇会是第一个
I didn't think Abruzzi'd be the first to go.
我觉得一定还会有很多意外的事情
I have a feeling we're in for lots of surprises.
他们说我们还有七个人
They said seven are still out there.
看来我们伪造死亡被识破了
So much for faking our deaths.
我们赢得了一些时间  所以还是有价值的
I bought us some time-- that's what counts.
还有多远?
How much further?
七八十英里
70,80 miles.
好的 我们下午就能到KK农场了
Good. Means we should be hitting the Double K Ranch by this afternoon. Or we can keep driving,
我们可以接上LJ
pick up LJ
然后一直开到巴拿马
and hit Panama.
我们不能去巴拿马
We can't hit Panama!
我们哪儿都不能去  什么都不能做
We can't hit anything! We can't do anything
在没有钱的情况下
without the money.
我们要找到查尔斯藏钱的地方
We need to find Charles's stash.
我知道其他人也在想着这事
I know some other guys who are thinking the same thing.
钱就埋在KK农场的一个地窖里
The money is buried under a silo at the Double K Ranch
就在犹他州的图勒镇外
just outside of Tooele,Utah.
查票
Tickets?
哦  在夏延的时候
Oh. Um,you know,when I was in Cheyenne,
我从口袋里把票拿出来的时候
I pulled my ticket out of the bag.
把它撕成了两半...
It tore in half,and...
我不知道另一半哪儿去了
I have no idea what happened to the other part.
他们没有补给你一张新的?
They didn't issue you a replacement?
没有啊 那位小姐  好像叫雪莉
No. The young lady-- I think-- her name was Sherry--
说剩下这半张也能用
she actually said that this half is okay
因为上面的条形码还在
because the bar code is on it.
但是你确实是需要一张完整的票
Well,you really need the whole ticket.
我当时就是想要避免这样的情况
This is exactly what I was trying to avoid.
但是她说  没问题的...
She said that everything would be fine because...
好吧  现在算了
That's okay. It'll do for now.
不过你务必要换一张新的
But make sure you ask for a replacement
当你到了普罗沃后
when you get to Provo.
我一定会的  谢谢
I definitely will. Thank you.
总会遇到些事情 是吧?
It's always something,huh?
哦 是的 我明白
Oh,God,I know.
我不想回家了
我真想我们就这样一直开车走
I wish we could keep driving.
我可不觉得你老爸会同意的
I don't think your Pops will be down for that.
这样不是很有趣吗?
Wouldn't it be fun?
我们可以去...
We could go to...
夏威夷?
Hawaii?
哈 你不能
Yo,you can't
开车去夏威夷
drive to Hawaii.
我知道
I know.
我只是说说
I'm just saying
我希望
I wish.
呃
Whoa,whoa.
不...不要去开 他们会走的
No,no. Don't get it. They'll leave.
我只是看看是谁
Just let me see who it is
是个警察
It's a cop.
不 不 不 不 不
No,no,no,no,no. Whoa,whoa,whoa.
很抱歉打扰你  小姐
Sorry to disturb you,ma'am.
你有没有见过这个人?
Have you happened to see this person?
昨天晚上我们收到线索
Last night we got a few phone calls
说他在这附近出现
that he was spotted in the area.
所以我们在挨家挨户地调查
So we're going door-to-door.
你们为什么要找他?
Why are you looking for him?
他一两天前
He escaped from prison in Illinois
从伊利诺斯州一所监狱越狱
a couple of days ago.
你有没有见过他?
And you see him?
没有
No.
没见过
He doesn't look familiar.
你确定?
Are you sure?
是的  我确定
Yeah. I'm sure.
好吧
All right.
谢谢 打扰你了
Thanks for your time.
呃
Whoa.
嘿 嘿
Whoa,whoa,whoa.
这不是...
This ain't...
不是你想的那样 好吗?
This is not what you think,all right?
嘿
Look.
听我说 这...
Listen to me,this...
听...我说
Just... listen.
好吗?
Okay?
我仅仅只是
All I did
偷了一张棒球卡
was steal a baseball card.
好吗? 我并不像那儿的其他人
Okay? I'm not like those other fools up in there.
我现在想去散个步 难道不行么?
I'm gonna go for a walk,okay?
听着... 我会把我的钥匙留这儿
Listen... I'm gonna leave my keys right here.
等到我回来的时候
And when I come back,
我的车子自然会不见
my car will be gone.
我想
I'm sure,
几个小时后
in a few hours,
警察会在某个地方找到它的...
they'll find it somewhere...
被扔在了路边
abandoned.
等等  等等
Wait. Wait.
我也不希望我现在这样子
I wish it could be different.
我得走了
I have to go.
这就是图雷
"Too-le."
我想应该是图勒镇
I think it's "To-ill-uh."
这么个小镇
Hell of a town.
小点好
Small is good.
那个农场找起来就容易点
Means the ranch'll be easier to find.
我们要做的就是拿到钱
All we got to do is get that money
然后在日落前离开
and we'll be out of here by nightfall.
对
Right.
哦 长官 斯科菲尔德的车祸化验报告出来了
Oh,sir. Soil test came back from Scofield's crash.
不用进一步的证明
Not that you need any more proof,but...
他现在还逍遥法外
he really went out of his way this time.
还有什么消息?
What else do you have?
内布拉斯加州有人被暴力攻击
Man was violently assaulted in Nebraska
根据搭车旅行者的描述 像是帝博格干的
by a hitchhiker matching Bagwell's description.
他正在沿着80州际公路往西逃
He was headed west on the I-80.
俄马哈把照片排好了
Omaha's putting together a photo lineup.
有什么关于斯科菲尔德的?
What do you have on Scofield?
其他人有没有
What does anybody
关于斯科菲尔德的消息?
have on Scofield?
嗯 我从他的硬盘里
Uh,I've got some results
得到了些信息
from his hard drive.
就是从河里打捞上来的那个硬盘
The one recovered from the river.
我们可以运用
We were able to use
扇形编辑器去恢复主要信息
the sector editor to restore the master boot.
然后...
So from that...
我不管你怎么做的
I don't care how you did it.
你找到了什么?
What do you have?
超过一半的缓冲容量
More than half the contents of the buffer.
接近百分之60
About 60%.
但分布都很零散
It looks pretty random.
全部打印出来  放到我桌子上
Print it up. All of it. I want it on my desk.
呃  你猜怎么着?
Well,guess what?
列表上没有KK农场
No listing for a Double K Ranch.
请问
Excuse me.
你知道KK农场在哪儿吗?
You know where I might find a Double K Ranch?
什么?
What you call it?
KK农场
Double K Ranch.
不知道
No.
你是这一带的人么?
You from around here?
是的  从小到大一直在这
Yeah. Born and raised.
没有什么KK什么农场
There's no Double-nothin'.
好了  谢谢
Great. Thank you.
看来韦斯特莫兰德在临死前
Looks like Westmoreland
耍了你一通
spent his last breath blowing smoke up your ass.
还有个方法
There's one way to find out.
这个县一定会保存有财产记录
The county keeps property records.
上面会用标尺标明所有地点
Every plot is mapped out
是公共档案
with dimensions. It's public record.
如果这里有财税办公室的话
But if there is a tax assessor's office here,
那一定是在这里 市政大楼
it's gonna be in there,the Municipal Building.
那里有警察巡逻的
快讯
Dispatch.
有人...有人今天早上偷走了我的车
Someone...someone stole my car this morning.
我在莲花汽车旅馆  80州际公路上
I'm at the Lotus Motel off Interstate 80
你有没有看到是谁偷走的?
Did you see who took it?
没有  我出去散步了
No. I went out for a walk
回来的时候  已经不见了
and when I came back,it was gone.
今天早上?
This morning?
为什么之前不打电话来?
Why didn't you call before?
我... 我也不知道
I... I don't know.
哈罗!
芝加哥伊利诺州
克里曼先生
Mr. Kellerman.
金姆先生
Mr. Kim.
能在芝加哥见到你 真是巧啊
Surprised to see you in Chicago.
只是来看下进展
Just looking for updates.
唐克雷蒂 莎拉  我正在处理
Sara Tancredi. I'm on it.
你就花了你所有的时间去追查她?
Is pursuing her the best use of your time?
没错
It is.
她和斯科菲尔德还有联系
She's in contact with Scofield.
昨天他们通电话的时候我就在旁边
I was there when he called yesterday.
我们有了她  就能找到斯科菲尔德
We stay with her,she takes us right to him,
找到斯科菲尔德  就找到布伦斯
he takes us to Burrows.
得了
All right.
既然你那么自信
If you're that confident.
是的
I am.
我会告诉总统
I'll let the president know.
我会直接和总统联系
I contact the president directly.
我来联系她
I'll contact her.
有任何进展通知我一下
Keep me posted.
如果你要找回你的尊严
If you want to restore your dignity,
你就必须做出行动
you need to take action.
痛改前非不仅仅是说句对不起就行了
Making amends requires much more than saying "I'm sorry."
你需要学着改变自己
It means learning to change.
道歉只是第一步
The apology is just the first step.
最重要的是在你道歉的时候
The most important thing is that you display honesty,
你必须诚实
courage and compassion
要有勇气和同情心
when you extend your apologies.
你要做的就是去赢得别人的原谅
You need to earn your forgiveness.
我们星期五再继续讨论
We'll talk about it more on Friday.
我有个好主意
I've got a great idea.
怎么说?
What's that?
既然你那么喜欢
Since you are such a fan
外面买的蓝莓派
of lame,store-bought blueberry pie,
我打算今晚亲自做个你喜欢的给你
I am going to bake you a real pie of your choice tonight.
不用了
I can't.
现在除了我的医生外
I really don't need to be seeing anyone right now
我真的不想见任何人
who isn't my therapist.
我最近也像个隐居者
I've been a hermit lately,too.
我的搭档丹尼尔外出谈生意去了
My partner Daniel's away on business.
每晚我都独自一人
I've been sitting around every night by myself.
有点可怜啊
Kind of pathetic.
真的很抱歉
I am so sorry.
我以为你是说...
I thought you meant...
啊...
Um...
我以为...
I thought...
派...
The-The pie...
哦！
Oh,no.
我太自以为是  不 我就是在讲蓝莓派
That's my ego. No,I was really talking about...
是的
Pie? Yeah.
真正的蓝莓 我们可以自己动手做派
Actual blueberries. Like we'd make pie and watch
看《油炸绿番茄》(电视节目)   我明白
Fried Green Tomatoes.I get it,
我明白
I get it.
我是这个镇里最好的戒了毒的厨师
I'm the best ex-junkie cook in this town.
谢谢 我得... 得回家搞搞卫生了
Thank you. I just... I-I got to clean my apartment.
乱的一塌糊涂 我知道这听起来像个借口 但不是
It's disgusting,and I realize that sounds like an excuse; it's not.
不不不 我明白
No,no,no,I get it.
你去做该做的吧
Um... you do what you got to do.
祝你有个愉快的夜晚
Have a good night.
送我一程怎样？
Do you deliver?
下一份材料
Next batch.
放在桌上就好了
Just... put it on the desk.
看出些眉目了吗?
Does any of this stuff mean anything?
没 迟点再说
I don't know. Ask me later.
他是个天才还是个疯子?
Think he's a genius or a whack-job?
这还用问吗？
I think we answered that question
我们都派了上百个探员来调查这案子了
when we assigned a hundred agents to the case.
你能不能过去帮我把剩余的材料都弄好?
So why don't you go and get me the rest of it,huh?
明白了没?
Does that work for you?
多幸运啊
Alackaday.
居然碰到了个同伴啊
I just found me an In-betweener.
这么急 上哪啊?
Where you going in such a hurry,huh?
关你屁事
None of your beeswax,yo.
我知道你去哪
I know where.
去我们这群人都想去的那个地方么
Same place as every other man who was in that room that night.
大家都来了 大团圆啊
They all comin' around here for a big family reunion
去KK农场
at the Ku Klux Ranch.
除非他们还没到
If they ain't here already.
镇上的人不是都说没听说过这地方吗？
Ain't no country folk in this town ever heard of the Double K Ranch.
你好像被误导了
Seems like you've been misinformed.
确实有个地方叫这名字
Indeedy there is a Double K.
关键要看谁先到那了 是吧?
It's just a matter of who gets there first,all right?
情况紧急啊 伙计
The stars are going to collide in Tooele,my friend.
你会需要我帮助的
You're going to need me on your side.
这儿可不是监狱 你以为呢?
This ain't Fox River,all right?
我不需要任何...
I don't need any...
要知道...
As you can see...
我需要你
I need you.
拿开你的脏手 变态老
Get your grubby paws off me,you freak.
我不是你的挖掘工
I ain't your ditch digger.
我不需要你的帮助
I don't want nothing from you.
什么都不需要
I don't need nothing.
你会要的...
You might...
如果有个人知道
if a man knew where
你要找的地方在哪
he was supposed to be looking.
内华达州 拉斯维加斯100里外
喂 喂
Hi,hi.
赫克托·阿维拉 和玛丽克鲁兹·德尔加多
Are you having the Hector Avila
的婚礼是在你们那举行吗?
and Maricruz Delgado wedding today?
阿维拉
Avila.
不是?那好吧 谢谢
No? Okay,thanks.
喂
Hi.
赫克托·阿维拉 和玛丽克鲁兹·德尔加多
Are you having the Hector Avila
的婚礼是在你们那举行吗?
and Maricruz Delgado wedding today?
阿维拉
Avila.
德尔加多
Delgado.
真的?
Really?
什么时候?
When?
镇定点  我们十分钟后就能出来了
Stay calm. We'll be out in ten minutes.
一个个来
One at a time.
可以了
Clear.
等下
Back up.
戴了表吗?
Are you wearing a watch?
啊 是的
Uh,yeah.
祝你愉快
Have a nice day.
谢谢
Thanks.
这正是我们要的
This is exactly what we need.
这份地图非常详细
It's a map of every parcel of land.
地形学 建筑体...
Topography,buildings...
一切都有
everything.
卡尔 可可辛 KK
Karl Kokosing. Double K.
我不喜欢那家伙看我们的眼神
I don't like the way this guy is looking at us.
1213页
1213.
1213页在哪?
Where's 1213?
赛泊恩 小姐 我得和你谈谈
Ms. Sebern,I need to speak with you.
快点 伙计
Come on,man,
我们得走人了
we got to roll now.
赛泊恩  小姐
Ms. Sebern.
快点 拿到地图了吗?
Come on. You got the map?
没有
No
让人捷足先登了
Somee else does.
只能这么说 有人比我们抢先了一步
Someone got here before us. It's the only explanation.
这个混蛋居然还活着
Son of a bitch is still alive.
嗨  兄弟!
Hey,pretty!
你打算干嘛
What are you going
尖叫 伙计?
to do,scream,man?
他妈的...
How the hell...
你居然还活着?
are you still breathing?
你的手怎么成这样了?
What the hell did you do to your hand?
轻点 轻点
Easy,easy...
我刚刚完成了一些事情
I recently had some work done.
地图去哪了?
Where's the map?!
轻点 轻点  我没拿地图
Easy,easy... I don't have it.
地图在哪里? 我告诉你了
Well,where is it? I'm telling you,
我没拿地图
I don't have it.
我没有  明白吗?你刚才在那里
I don't have it,all right?! You were there.
我们看见你了
We saw you.
我到的时候地图已经不见了
It was gone when I got there.
所以把你的爪子从我身上拿开
Now why don't you keep your pooch away from me.
我把我知道的全都告诉你
I'll tell you everything I know.
是那小子干的 他拿走了地图
It's the kid. He has it.
我今天早上遇到他
I saw him this morning
我需要帮助
and I needed some help.
于是我们就做了个交易 明白吗?
We made a deal,all right?
他说他来挖
He said that he would dig.
我就告诉他地图在哪里?
I told him where we could get a map.
哪个小子?
What kid?
最好是什么也不用做
The best thing to do is nothing.
什么都不做？我就准备这样通过
That's how I'm going to get the U.S. Senate
参议院来做副总统的
to confirm my vice president,do nothing?
让他们看看你能胜任
Shows them you can do the job.
我女儿的电话
It's my daughter.
先生 我们要谈谈关于您的女儿
Sir,we need to talk about your daughter.
她怎么了?
What about her?
媒体上都是关于福克斯河 的报道
Well,the media is all over this Fox River situation.
我们认为您最好
We think it would be best
能跟她保持距离
if you could distance yourself from her
别再跟我说这个了
If I hear this one more time
我把她保释出来就离开了
I paid her bail,I walked away.
我已经跟她保持距离了
I have distanced myself.
失陪一下
Give me a minute.
嗨 爸爸 是我
Hey,Dad,it's me.
等你有空的时候
Um,when you get a chance,
我希望能跟你谈点事情
I really need to talk to you about something.
事实上很多事?
Um,actually a lot of things.
最重要的就是...
Uh,the most important one is that,um...
我要向你道歉
I owe you an apology.
我 我知道我最近...
I,uh,I realize that I've made things difficult
给你惹了不少麻烦
for you lately... um...
我想我应该...
...and I want
要负起责任来
to take responsibility for that.
再联络  再见
Um...call me back. Bye.
你好
Hi.
我知道我来早了 但我带了晚饭过来 进来吧
I know I'm early,but I brought dinner. Come on in.
你不是素食主义者 对吧? 不是的
You're not a vegetarian,are you? No.
把门顺带一下
Just shut that behind you.
让我查查邮件好吗?
You mind if I check my e-mail?
好呀 给你
No,not at all. Here.
啊 你人真好  非常感谢
Oh,you're so kind. Thank you. Absolutely.
手头有笔么?
Do you happen to have a pen handy?
有
Yeah.
实在太感谢了 真是麻烦你了
Thank you so much. I'm so sorry to bother you.
没关系的 我这有铅笔和记事本
Not at all. Look,I have a little pencil and a pad.
谢谢你
Thank you.
先生?
Sir?
什么?
Yeah.
夏延那没有雪莉这位小姐?
There's no Sherry in Cheyenne.
你的票不能乘车
Your ticket is not valid for travel.
哎 等下
Oh,well,hold on now.
不可能 不可能
Tha-That can't be right. That can't be right.
劳驾让一下
Excuse me for a second.
好
Sure.
好吧 听着 老兄
All right now,listen,brother.
我就直话直说了
I'm gonna give it to you straight.
那个.. 我破产了 行了吧?
Listen,listen,I-I'm broke,okay?
这是真的
That's the truth.
我刚才又惹上麻烦了
And I just ran into some trouble a while back and...
我就是想把事情赶快搞定
I'm just really trying to pull it all together now.
明白吗?
You understand?
你再等5分钟把这些
You can tell it all to the authorities
告诉当地警察局吧
in about five minutes.
拜托 老兄
Oh,come on,brother.
咱们用不着...  太晚了
We don't have to get the authorities... Oh,it's too late.
他们已经在下一站等着了
They're already waiting at the next stop.
这两位警官
These guys here,
他们将陪你一起坐到下一站
they're gonna sit with you until we stop.
明白 明白
I understand. I understand.
嗨!
Hey!
嗨 你不能进去
Hey,you can't go in there!
好了 有可靠消息说看到富兰克林
Okay,we've got a confirmed sighting on Franklin.
在爱达荷州的普雷斯顿 从一辆运行中的火车中跳了出来
Jumped out of a moving train in Preston,Idaho.
一个从芝加哥来的老黑到爱达荷来干什么?
What is a black man from Chicago doing in Idaho?
他准是迷路了
He's got to be lost.
富兰克林在爱达荷的普雷斯顿
Franklin's in Preston,Idaho.
巴格威尔在内布拉斯加
Bagwell's in Nebraska.
两人都没渡过密西西比河
And both men have never been across the Mississippi.
探亲访友?我不这么想
Visiting friends and family? I don't think so.
也不是...
And not...
南下去边境
south of the border.
他们在西行?我们要搞明白...
They're due west and we need to know...
为什么
why.
下车
Out.
怎么了 朋友?
What's going on,friends?
你刚说特纳?朝哪个方向去了?
Where did you say Tweener was headed?
从大路走了 他应该是去找铲子了
Up on the main drag. He was supposed to find a shovel.
进去
In.
不
No.
不 不 不
No,no,no.
进!
In!
你们还回来的是吧?
You coming back,right?
你们得回来!
You coming back?!
对
Yep.
你们俩个!
Hey,you guys!Hey!
拜托 我可以帮你们!
Come on,man,I'm gonna help you here!
我当时正在开越野车
I was on my ATV,and I was hauling ass.
我紧跟着她屁股后面 我拔枪出来
I was right on her tail,and I pulled out my gun
乓!那畜牲像棵树一样倒下了
and blam! That bitch treed herself,
我一枪就打中了
and I brought her down in one shot.
秤分量没?
What'd she weigh?
至少一百...
Least a hunny.
也许十分之一
Maybe one-ten.
要是你愿意下次来找我们
Come on out and see us if you want.
那就有意思了
It's gonna be a good time.
是啊 我应该会去的
Yeah,I just might do that.
嗨,你打算挖什么?
hey,now,what you digging?
在我爷爷家的院子挖点东西
Uh...some stuff in my grandpa's yard.
你要是挖得深点的话我后房有把大铲子
We got a bigger one in the back if you're going deep.
不用了
No,
这个就可以了
this will do.
妈的 要是我不认识你的话
Damn it if I don't know you from somewhere.
也许我认识你爷爷
Maybe I know your grandpa.
不是吧 老兄
I doubt it,man.
他...一个月前搬来这里...所以...
He moved here,like,a month ago,so...
他叫什么名字?
What's his name?
他叫爷爷
His name's Grandpa.
行了吧 老兄 你帮我把这些捆一下行吗?
A'ight? Look,man,can you just ring this up?
我得走了
I gotta get out of here.
小事一桩 哥们
Sure thing,fella.
我给你捆上
I'll ring it up.
现在就给你捆上
I'll ring it right now.
我在电视上见过你
I know where I seen you On the TV.
你是福克斯河的逃犯之一
You're one of them Fox River boys.
你搞错了 老兄
You got it wrong,man.
不 我想我没错
No,I think I got it right.
打烊了
We're closed!
抱歉 哥们
Sorry,bud.
今天收工早了点
Closing up early today.
等一下
Hold on.
站着别动
Stay right there.
你完蛋了 就像你那哥们 你个狗杂种
You're going down,just like your buddy,you son of a...
那小子在哪?
Where's the kid?
Where's the kid?!
他在后边
He's back here.
起来
Get up.
起来 猛男
Come on,tough guy.
走
Let's go.
玛丽克鲁兹
Maricruz.
宝贝 开门
Baby,open up.
是我 是我 别出声 好吗?
It's me. It's me,okay?
费尔南多 你怎么在这里?
Fernando,what are you doing here?
我...你不能在这
I... You can't be here.
我知道泰瑞莎,我刚...
I know,Theresa. I just got...
你妹妹呢?我要见玛丽克鲁兹
Where's your sister? I need to see Maricruz.
她在和爸妈一起照相
She's getting her picture taken with my mom and dad.
婚礼2点半开始  我现在就要见她
The wedding's at 2:30. I need to see her now.
你得离开
You have to go.
她是我孩子的母亲啊 泰瑞莎.
She's the mother of my kid,Theresa.
求求你
Please.
你不想她嫁给赫克托 是吗?是吧?
You don't want her to marry Hector,do you? Do you?
我试试看能不能找她来
I'll go see if I can go get her.
在这里等着
Wait in here.
好的
Okay.
兰斯我有个问题要问你
Lance,I got a question for you.
问吧?
Yes?
你知道我是谁么?
Do you know who I am?
我昨晚碰巧看了新闻 我知道
Uh...I happened to see the news last night,yes.
嗨 这没关系
Hey,I don't care.
我也有不想让人知道的事
I've got some skeletons in my closet,too.
只是有些批着鲜亮的外衣
One of them wears a dress.
谢谢
Thank you.
感谢你没对我说三道四
I appreciate your lack of judgment.
在我看来
From what I can tell,
你一点也没错
you didn't do anything wrong,
但这不关我事
but it's none of my business.
你不用跟我说
And you don't need to talk about it.
整个事情...
The whole thing just...
我从来没想过会变成这样
I never meant for it to happen.
好 你不用回答这个问题
Okay,you do not need to answer this question.
嗯?
Hmm?
但是你当时和那个家伙 好像...
But were you and that guy,like,uh...
你说的 我可以不回答
You're right,I don't want to talk about it.
吃完了?
You done?
是啊
Yeah.
他现在在逃 你会不会...
Does it worry you that he's...
担心?
out there?
稍等片刻
Give me one second.
爸爸
Dad.
莎拉
Sara,hi.
我收到你的留言
I got your message.
请进来吧
Should we... Please,come in.
兰斯
Uh,Lance,
这位 他是我爸 法兰克
this is,uh,my father Frank.
您好
How do you do?
爸 这是我朋友兰斯
Uh,Dad,this is my friend Lance.
很荣幸见到您 先生 我给您投票了
Pleasure to meet you,sir. I voted for you.
谢谢 深表感激
Well,thank you. I appreciate that.
莎拉 我想我该走了
Sara,I can take off.
不 没关系
No,no need.
马上就好
It'll only take a minute.
那就来我办公室吧
Why don't you step into my office
你请随意
and you make yourself at home.
好
Sure.
那...
So,uh...
在我的疗程里 嗯...
So,in my program,um...
我们说了很多关于改过的事情
we've been talking a lot about making amends,
我也想了很多关于...
and I've been thinking a lot about,um...
关于一些
about some of
我最近所作的选择
the choices I've made lately,
我也知道那影响了你
and I know that that affects you.
呃...
Um...
我 我想告诉你
and I... I wanted to tell you
我很抱歉
that I'm sorry.
你不用道歉
You don't have to say you're sorry.
不 我要道歉
Yeah,I do.
很难理解
And it must be hard to understand
我为什么这么做
why I did it.
我当时根本不知道是我把这些人
Um,I had no idea that I was putting these guys
放跑的
back out on the street.
我以为我是在救一个无辜的人...
I thought I was saving the life of an innocent man and...
我知道你没有看我给你的
And I know that you didn't read the information
关于林肯·布伦斯的信息  但他是无辜的...
I gave you on Lincoln Burrows,but he is innocent and...
很多卷入此事的人现在都死了
a lot of the people involved right now are dead.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
这不是我给你打电话的原因
This isn't why I called you.
我很好
I'm fine...
但我很害怕
but I'm scared.
莎拉...
Sara...
我会帮你熬过去的
I'm gonna help you through this.
我们一起会熬过去
We're gonna get through this together.
谢谢
Thank you.
我保证
I promise.
克里曼
Kellerman.
我们根据你的要求进行了追踪
We ran that trace you requested.
你找到什么了?
What'd you get?
这个号码打不通
The line is disconnected.
之前是谁的?
Whose was it?
表面上看 谁的也不是
Apparently,no one's.
什么意思?
What does that mean?
这个号码已经有17年没被用过了
It's been out of service for 17 years.
费尔南多
Fernando.
她在哪?
Where is she?
冷静 冷静
Oh,calm down. Calm down.
她会下楼和你谈的
She's gonna come down and talk to you.
她马上就来了
She's on her way down right now.
我们很早就认识了
You and I got history.
是一家人
We're family.
出于这层关系
And out of respect for that,
我会让她自己做决定的
I'm gonna let her make her own decision.
我一定会带她走的
I'm not leaving without her.
这应该让玛丽克鲁兹决定
That's for Maricruz to decide.
你让她听够了你的废话
You've been filling her head with all this crap.
她是个聪明的女孩
She's a smart girl.
我个人认为她
I personally don't think she's gonna
不会想跟你逃一辈子 但还是看着吧
want to live her life on the run,but we'll see.
你知道 她不爱你 我现在不想讨论这些
You know,she doesn't love you. Yeah,I don't want to get into that right now.
你不会抚养我的孩子的 我知道
You're not raising my kid.
听起来不怎么舒服啊?老弟
That don't sound good,cuz.
玛丽克鲁兹!
Maricruz!
宝贝!
Baby!
你得快走
Mari. You have to go.
她在哪? 费尔南多  警察来了!
Wh-Where is she? Please,Fernando,they're coming!
你跟她说我在这吗? 说了吗?!
Did you tell her I was here? Did you?!
玛丽克鲁兹...
Maricruz...
马宏
Mahone.
我马上下来
I'll be right down.
马宏先生
Mr. Mahone.
药在哪?
Where are they?
我很不容易才拿到这些
Had a hard time getting my hands on these.
其实看医生很容易啊
It'd be easier to go to a doctor,
告诉他你需要一些镇静药     医生会做记录的
tell him you need something to calm your nerves. Doctors take notes.
所以我跟你买
That's why I have a deal with you.
原来如此 我还以为我们的交易已经结束了
The way things been going,I thought maybe our deal was over.
你没再问我关于希尔斯的事情了
You don't ask me about Shales no more.
那个交易已经结束了
That part of our deal is over.
我不再需要那件案子的消息了
I no longer need an informant on the case.
你不是一直想找到他吗?
Thought that's all you cared about was finding him.
你不可能抓住所有人
You can't get them all.
如果你想 我会留意的
If you want,I can keep an ear out on the street.
咪达唑仑 1500 毫克每个月
Midazolam. 1,500 milligrams every 30 days.
我只要这些
That's all I want from you.
你明白了吗?
We understand each other?
你不付钱给我?
You gonna pay me for it?
给你
Right there.
你在这儿干什么?
What are you doing here?
来找你 兄弟
We had to come for you,buddy.
你怎么知道的?
How'd you know?
帝博格
T-Bag.
交出地图吧
Hand over the map.
什么?
What?
地图...给我
The map. Hand it over.
他说在我这里?
我们要算一下账了
We are going to sort this out right now.
告诉我这不是那地图
Tell me that's not what I know it is.
是的
It is.
但别担心 在毁掉它之前
But don't worry,before I destroyed it
我已经记在我脑子里了
I committed it to my photographic memory.
从一个骗子口中听到的话
Coming from a compulsive liar,
要让我相信有点困难
I find that a little hard to believe.
我想把它纹在身上的  但没有时间
I'da tattooed it to my body but I didn't have the time.
你如果想搜查一个人
Whenever you strip search a lifer,
你应该先看看他的钱包
you should always check his coin purse.
告诉我们钱在哪?
Tell us where the money is.
现在让我们和解 怎么样?
Now let's not dissolve into threats,all right?
我有条好路可以走
I'm going to take the high road here
我建议一个对我们都好的安排
and suggest a mutually beneficial arrangement.
我提供信息
I have the information,
而你们有人手可以
you have the manual requirements
挖出韦斯特莫兰德的宝藏
necessary to unearth Westmoreland's buried booty.
我们搭档
We're partners.
为什么这样?
And why is that?
因为现在
'Cause as of this moment,
我就是你们的地图
I'm your map.
我们四个人平分那笔钱 是吗?
So then,yo,we split it four ways,right?
错  进去
Wrong. Get in.
哇  哇  哇
Whoa,whoa,whoa.
你还不值1万5呢
You're not worth 1.5.
进去   好的
Get in. Okay.
对不起 需要点什么?
Excuse me. Can I help you?
哦  是的
Oh. Yeah.
抱歉  是的  呃... 哦!
Sorry,yeah. Uh... whoo!
太热了
It's hot.
我想知道你的房车卖多少钱?
I was really wondering how much you selling your RV for.
也许你买不起
Probably out of your price range.
拜托 说吧
Come on,give me a shot.
4万美元
$40,000.
呃 怎么说呢
Look,I tell you what.
我过几天再来买 怎么样?
I'll be back in a couple days,okay?
我不能就为你留着
I can't hold it for you.
我说了我会回来的
I said I'll be back.
带着现金
With cash.
好车
Nice bike.
婚礼在 2:30举行  费尔南多
The wedding's at 2:30,Fernando.
我们得到 费尔南多 苏克雷 的消息
We just got confirmation on Fernando Sucre.
他在2:00的时候出现在拉斯维加斯
He was in Las Vegas around 2:00.
而后一个加油站服务员发现一个骑摩托车的人
Then a gas station attendant
符合费尔南多 苏克雷的描述
spotted a guy on a bike matching his description
在 麦斯基德...
in Mesquite...
一个小时以后
an hour later.
往西走  那和巴格威尔 与 富兰克林 是一个方向的
Out west,just like Bagwell and Franklin.
是的  但是苏克雷是朝东走的
Yeah,but he was heading east.
巴格威尔在内布拉斯加州的80州际公路上 向西内布拉斯加州
And Bagwell's in Nebraska on I-80 heading west.
富兰克林的火车朝西走的
And Franklin's train was heading west,
但是他跳到...
but he jumped off to the...
啊...哈哈
sou...
你知道 D.B.库珀?
You know D.B. Cooper?
是 是 劫机犯  劫机犯
Yeah,yeah,the hijacker. Hijacker.
但没找到他
But he was never found.
是的 但是他肯定在哪个地方
Yeah,but he's got to be somewhere,right,
因为有人在波特兰劫机
because someone hijacked that plane in Portland
然后在西北太平洋跳机
and jumped out over the Pacific Northwest.
两天后有人被逮住了
And someone was arrested two days later
在亚利桑那州的比斯比
in Bisbee,Arizona.
不是同一个人 是同一个人
Not the same guy. Same guy.
同一个人  他的膝盖受伤了
Same guy who was treated for a broken knee
在盐湖城附近某家免费诊所治疗
in a free clinic somewhere around Salt Lake City.
同一个人在离边界十英里的地方
Same guy whose Nova blew a head gasket ten miles short of the border
同一个人开着偷来的车差点逃脱
Same guy who almost got away with a stolen car,
但他在比斯比撞到了一个女人
but he ran a woman down in Bisbee.
以交通肇事罪被捕
Vehicular manslaughter
用的名字是查尔斯 韦斯特莫兰德
Arrested and booked as Charles Westmoreland.
但是他身上没有钱
But he didn't have the money on him.
这就意味着...
Which means...
他把钱藏在他经过的某个地方了
he got rid of it somewhere along the way.
等等 等等 这是事实? 你发现了这一切?
Wait,wait,this is fact? You figured all this out?
不是  是斯科菲尔德发现的
No. Scofield did.
这就是为什么他会带着这个老头一起
That's why he was bringing the old man along.
那些钱在犹他州
The money's in Utah.
所以他们都要去那里
And they're all going to get it.
你知道吗?在...泰国
You know,in,uh,Thailand
他们有个黑市
they got a black market
那里你能做任何外科手术
where you can get any kind of surgery you need,
甚至手的移植
even a hand transplant.
你有毛病 你知道吗?  继续开
You're sick,you know that. Keep going.
转弯处就在这儿附近什么地方
The turnoff's just up here somewhere.
过不过那小路?
Before or after Sheep Road?
怎么了 你忘记了?
What's the matter,Theodore,did you forget?
我怎么会忘记那小路的?
How could I forget a road called Sheep?
过的
It's after.
你们不觉得心里很暖吗?
Don't you feel all warm inside
现在我们在一起了
now that we're working together?
我们不是在一起
We aren't working together.
你在这里只是借你的一只手而已
You're just here to lend a hand.
好了 减速
Now,slow down.
就在那里 那条小路
That was it,that little bitty road
后退
right back there.
离这还有多远?
How far is it from here?
如果我记得没错的话还有1/4英里
Quarter mile if I remember the scale properly.
走吧
Start walking.
法兰克?
Frank?
好的 我快准备好了
Yeah,I'm almost ready.
航班是几点钟?
What time did you say the flight was?
8:00
8:00.
听着 相比其他人
Listen,I hope you get this nomination
我更希望你得到这个任命,但是...
more than anyone,but...
你要准备好
be prepared.
这个布伦斯的事情很棘手
This Burrows thing may steamroll.
好吧 我们等着 就像你说的
Well,we'll wait it out,just like you said.
问题是有很多麻烦
Problem is too many headlines.
他的律师 尼克 萨维恩 已经死了
His lawyer Nick Savrinn's already dead.
他的儿子由于两起谋杀案正在等候审判
His kid's awaiting trial for double homicide.
而现在他的主辩律师失踪了
And now his lead counsel is classified as missing.
哦,她是失踪了还是死了?
Well,is she missing or is she dead?
我只是认为你在去华盛顿之前应该都想清楚
I just thought you should know before you go to Washington.
布鲁斯 有什么事情和这有关?
Bruce,is there something connecting all of this?
最好你不要问那么多问题
It's probably best you don't ask a whole lot of questions.
现在往哪儿走?
Where now?
往前直走
Right up there.
这山坡就是财产的边界线
The hill borders the property.
KK农场就在山的那一边
KK's on the other side.
我拿到钱做的第一件事
First thing I'm gonna do with the money?
买双新鞋
Buy new shoes.
第二件  墨西哥玉米卷
Second thing: tacos.
第三件  冰啤酒
Third thing: ice cold beer.
第四件  一点牙膏
Fourth thing: a little toothpaste.
马宏
Mahone.
马宏长官 你的车子已经开出来了
Agent Mahone,your car's out front,sir.
去犹他的航班还有1小时
The flight to Utah leaves in an hour.
我就来 谢谢
I'll be there. Thank you.
第九件  洗个澡
Ninth thing: a shower.
第十件  睡个好觉
Tenth thing: a good night's sleep.
一家好旅馆 干净的床单
A nice hotel. Clean sheets.
看 树桩就是财产分界线的标志
Look,stakes marking the property line.
应该到了
Should be dead ahead.
看到地窖了吗?
Can you see the silo?
上面重新建造过了
The bastards built over it.
完了
It's gone.